Amanda Sheehan

32583 Bridgestone Dr, North Ridgeville, OH 44039 || (440) 525-4192 asheeha3@kent.edu || www.linkedin.com/in/amanda-sheehan-a2254b14a/

Professional Summary

Hard-working student pursuing a degree in computer information systems due to a passion for technology and helping others. Committed to producing my best work through attention to detail and a diligent work ethic while also working cohesively with others to ensure the optimal result.

Technical Skills

Experience in Python, C++, C#, SQL, JavaScript, CSS, HTML

Education

KENT STATE UNIVERSITY, Kent, OH

Bachelor of Business Administration || Expected Graduation: May 2020 Major: Computer Information Systems || Minor: Computer Science

GPA: 3.885 || Honors Program

Work Experience

HYLAND SOFTWARE, Westlake, OH | May 2019—Present

Campus Ambassador

- Work with the HR recruiting team to inform fellow students about internship and job opportunities.
- Engage with students to help them learn about the benefit of Hyland internships and jobs

Professional Services and Consulting Intern

- Gain experience in SalesForce/FinancialForce by creating reports and dashboards.
- Utilize Quip to produce dashboards and scorecards and integrate with FinancialForce.
- Learn company specific methodologies through transferring and reviewing project documents.
- Work with individuals taking a leadership capstone to bring their ideas to fruition.

KENT STATE INSTRUCTIONAL RESOURCE CENTER, Kent, OH | May 2017 - Present

Operations Manager

- Fingerprint and submit information for background checks to the government.
- Calculate deposits biweekly and write up tax forms monthly.
- Aide students and faculty with minor technical difficulties.
- Oversee organization of office equipment and records and perform routine maintenance

MITCHELL'S HOMEMADE ICE CREAM, Avon, OH | February 2013 - August 2018

Team Leader

- Guided team members in following company procedures correctly and efficiently.
- Effectively completed work with self-motivation and enthusiasm.
- Ensured the shop's cleanliness and friendliness in order to provide a superior customer experience.
- Engaged with customers to evaluate their satisfaction and to discover where the store could improve.